taskstream.com 2019-04-14

# Watermark Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy for Watermark Solutions

Watermark has created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) in order to communicate its policies and practices relating to the collection, use and disclosure of information about you, the end user. Watermark has drafted this statement in order to convey a firm commitment to your privacy as an end user of the Watermark website, and all services supplied by Watermark connected therewith (the “Site” and the “Services,” respectively).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, which may be changed or updated periodically.

If you decide to use the Site, or by agreeing to the Watermark End User Agreement, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information on the terms described in this Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time.

##### What information does Watermark collect, and how?

In order to gain access to the Site and take advantage of the Services, you will need to provide information as part of a registration process, including your name. Watermark requests this information from you in order to enhance, quantify and measure your use of the Site. Our registration form will also ask you to give us your contact information (name, telephone number and email address) and you have the option of supplying demographic and other information (like Zip code, school district, grade level and subject you are in or you teach).

“Cookies” are small pieces of information transferred from a website to the hard drive of computers through your Internet browser. Most browsers automatically accept Cookies, but can be configured to refuse them. We may use Cookies in very limited instances for connection purposes on certain browsers. The information collected does not contain anything personal to the end user and is discarded daily. Third party websites, which can be accessed through links on the Site, may use Cookies and similar devices to collect information about users, including information relating to products and services accessed, or advertising clicked on by a user, and websites visited by a user after leaving their websites. Watermark shall not be responsible for such practices that take place once you leave the Site.

##### Disclosure of Information

Watermark actively seeks to comply with all applicable statutes and regulations regarding maintaining the confidentiality and privacy of information held by it, including but not limited to the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”). Watermark does not sell or otherwise transfer customer information to third-party marketing companies under any circumstances. It is Watermark’s policy not to share your personal information with any third parties, other than in the limited circumstances set out below.

Watermark enables you to comply with your privacy and confidentiality obligations. However, you must be aware of your own obligations under FERPA or any other statute, regulation or other legal or institutional rule regarding the release of confidential information and act accordingly. You may participate in a variety of online forums on the Site, submit work to others for evaluation, share work with colleagues, and/or publish work in Watermark or to the World Wide Web at large. Any information you disclose in these areas will be available to certain other end users, and may be collected and used by persons other than Watermark. You should not disclose any information that you do not want others to know on these areas of the Site. Watermark does not routinely monitor these areas, and you use forums and tools at your own risk. In addition, you may also provide us with information such as your name, subject and grade / university level that you are in or that you teach, contact email address (if supplied), lesson plans, assignments, work product, and assessment rubrics, that identifies your own content. This information will be available only to other individuals with Watermark IDs and passwords within your organization with permission to view it, UNLESS YOU CHOOSE TO PUBLISH IT ON THE WORLD WIDE WEB. Personal information such as addresses and phone numbers are NEVER published on the Site by Watermark and should not be by you unless you are sure that your audience is allowed to have such information.

Watermark provides various communication tools that enable users to share work with users and non-users of Watermark. Once you have shared work with a third party, Watermark no longer can control access to that work and can make no assurances as to the privacy of that work. Do not disclose or send information to third parties that you do not want others to know, use or publish in other forums.

Watermark may disclose your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, a subpoena or other legal process. We may also disclose such information as is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against a person or entity who may be violating Watermark’s Terms of Use (or such other agreements to which an end user is a party), or who may be causing injury to, or interfering with, other users of the Site and Services, or other third parties who may be harmed by such activities. In addition, in the event that all or part of Watermark’s assets are acquired by a third party, user information may be included in the transferred assets.

In certain circumstances, Watermark applications have been configured to allow for authorized users to access and copy file attachments from third party applications (i.e. Google Drive) that are applicable to the work being done in the Watermark product. After the authorized user selects the file, it is exported into file storage in the Watermark product. Once there, the file that originated in the third party application is subject to this privacy policy and treated identically to all other files stored in the Watermark applications.

##### Receiving Information and Surveys by Email

Watermark also provides you with the opportunity to receive information and take customer surveys related to the Site and Services, by email. If you do not want to receive such information by email, you may opt out of further communications sent by Watermark at any time by sending us an email at privacy@watermarkinsights.com or by calling us at 1.800.311.5656. Please note that we can only comply with requests relating to email communication sent by Watermark. If you no longer wish to receive further information by email from any third party, you will need to contact such third party directly to opt out of further communications being sent to you.

##### Links

The Site may contain links to third-party websites. When you click on these links, you will leave the Site, and will then be subject to the information collection practices of such third parties. Watermark has no control over the content, policies or actions of these websites, even if you are offered products or services on those websites because you are an end user of the Site and Services. The use of any information you may provide to third parties on other websites, or which such parties may otherwise collect on other websites, is not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should carefully review the privacy policies of any third-party websites and contact the operators of those websites if you have any questions about their use of your information. Watermark cannot be responsible for any third party, or its affiliates or agents, failing to use your information in accordance with such third party’s privacy policy, or any contractual or other legal obligations to which such third party, its affiliates or agents, may be subject.

##### Data Security

Watermark takes commercially reasonable security measures to protect information provided by you against unauthorized access and use. Upon upload, your data files may be scanned for viruses, and the Webmaster will be notified of any viruses found. Access to information is only authorized with the use of a valid password protection. Watermark also uses commercially reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with your web browser for any transactions conducted online using a credit card or other financial information you may provide to us. PLEASE BE AWARE, HOWEVER, THAT NO DATA TRANSMISSION OVER THE INTERNET IS 100% SECURE AND ANY INFORMATION DISCLOSED ONLINE CAN POTENTIALLY BE COLLECTED AND USED BY PARTIES OTHER THAN THE INTENDED RECIPIENT.

FURTHER, IN THE EVENT THAT YOU CHOOSE TO STORE ASSESSMENT DATA ON WATERMARK, BE AWARE THERE IS NO EXTANT SECURITY MEASURE THAT CAN PROVIDE A GUARANTEE OF COMPLETE DATA SECURITY.

##### Changes and Updates to Privacy Policy

By using the Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This policy reflects Watermark’s current business practices, and is subject to change and update. In the event of any such change or update, a revised policy will be posted on the Site, with the last date of update noted on the bottom of the page. Please check the Site periodically to remain informed of any changes or updates to our privacy policies and practices.

##### Changes and Access to Personal Information

You may ask Watermark to correct, update or delete information you have provided to us by sending an email to us at privacy@watermarkinsights.com, or send postal mail to Watermark, 71 West 23rd Street, New York, NY 10010. Please feel free to contact us with questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site.

##### GDPR

**What is GDPR?**  
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a Regulation in the making by which the European Commission intends to strengthen and unify data protection for individuals within the European Union (EU). It also addresses export of personal data outside the EU. The regulation became effective on May 25, 2018.

**Watermark’s Commitment**  
Watermark is committed to high standards of information security, privacy and transparency. We place a high priority on protecting and managing data in accordance with accepted standards including ISO 27001 and PCI-DSS. The company is complying with applicable GDPR regulations, most importantly as a data processor, while also working closely with our customers and partners to help them meet their contractual obligations as data controllers.

Watermark’s approach to preparing for GDPR is overseen by an internal cross-functional team. As a Company that always considered data security as one of our highest priorities, we will continue the policies that have been place for years. For example:

  1. Continuously improving on our on existing security and business continuity management systems. 
  2. Continuing to encrypt all data in transit and at rest. 
  3. Watermark will inform any and all client organizations promptly in the event of any incidents involving your users’ data. 
  4. Not collecting non-essential data from our clients within our products other than that necessary for us to provide our services. 

Going forward, Watermark is committed to the following additional items consistent with GDPR Compliance:

  1. We will be reviewing our existing contracts with data controllers, the use of sub-contractors and any data export arrangements and adding a Data Processing Addendum where deemed appropriate. 
  2. Offering enhanced client services to help our client organizations meet their obligations as Data Controllers. 

Effective Date: July 16, 2018

## Privacy Policy for Watermark’s Website, www.watermarkinsights.com

We at Watermark, (“Company,” “we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how your personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy related to our Website, www.watermarkinsights.com. By visiting or using the Website in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect and use your information in the following ways.

##### I. What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of Personal Information that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

##### II. What Information Does Company Collect?

We gather various types of information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this information to personalize and improve our Website, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain information, to analyze how users utilize the Website, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not share certain types of Personal Information with third parties. We collect the following types of information:

###### A. Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you provide to us. For example, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, job title, Institution, address, etc. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or take advantage of some of our Website’s features.

###### B. Information Collected Automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Website are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Website’s features. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Website), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Website, so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Website, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

###### C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; to send you promotional offers related to our business, or communicate with you about your use of the Website. Also, we may receive a confirmation and/or other information when you open an email from us. This confirmation and/or other information helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference through your account settings at https://go.taskstream.com/preference-center. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us by email, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website or any of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

##### III. Is Personal Information About Me Secure?

Any Personal Information you share with us is kept in our database and not shared to any third parties. The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

##### V. What Choices Do I Have?

As explained above, you can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register for events with us or to take advantage of some of the features of our Website.

##### VII. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website or sending you an email. Changes will become effective no sooner than thirty (30) days after they are posted or communicated to you. However, changes addressing new functions for the Services or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. Your continued use of the Services following such notification shall constitute your affirmative acknowledgement of the changes and your agreement to abide and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as amended. If at any time you choose not to accept the Privacy Policy, including following receipt of notification of any changes hereto, then please terminate your subscription to the Services through your Services account.

##### VIII. Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send a detailed message to info@watermarkinsights.com, and we will try to address your concerns.

Effective Date: July 16, 2018
